citm.com 2016-06-23

# Checks In The Mail - Online Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy has changed. This policy is effective as of August 1, 2013.**

Checks In The Mail is committed to protecting the privacy of our current and future customers. We utilize technology that gives you a powerful, safe ordering experience that we hope exceeds your expectations. We want to assure you that when Checks In The Mail asks for consumer information, it's done with the goal of improving our relationship.

The following statements will help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard information you provide to Checks In The Mail.

**Automatic Collection of Anonymous, Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
When you browse the Checks In The Mail website, you do so without revealing your identity. Personal information, including email address, is not collected without your awareness. For each visitor to our website, our servers recognize the website you came from.

Additional anonymous, non-personally identifiable information is automatically collected by cookies. Cookies are small alphanumeric identifier files that store information. They enable our systems to recognize your browser and computer, and to provide important features that personalize our site to make your shopping faster and easier. Information from cookies helps us serve you better and improve our website design by keeping track of your shopping experience as you navigate our site. In the order capture process, Checks In The Mail may use Cookies to track the order preferences of visitors to our site. Cookie information is anonymous, meaning that it does not tell us who owns or uses the computer on which the cookies are stored.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can use the majority of the features within our site. We recommend that you take full advantage of all the features we've designed to make shopping easy and fun by leaving your cookies enabled.

**Children**  
Our website is directed at adult consumers and guests. We do not knowingly solicit data from, or market to, children under age 13. Should children access our website, we are confident that parents will not judge any of the information provided as objectionable for viewing. If you are under 18, you may use the Checks In The Mail website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Website Links**  
Checks In The Mail is not responsible for the content, privacy practices or information practices employed by sites linked to or from our website. In most cases, links to non-Checks In The Mail websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of the Checks In The Mail website. 

**Disclosure of Individual Consumer Information**  
Checks In The Mail uses the information collected from you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Checks In The Mail may also use your information to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions in the future. We may use third party service providers to assist us in maintaining good consumer relations by communicating to you relevant announcements regarding exclusive sales, company information, and to conduct consumer surveys. We may also provide your information to third party service providers who assist us in fulfilling your order, as well as to financial institutions for customer verification and fraud prevention purposes. All of our third party service providers are required by contract not to otherwise disclose your personal information.

We **DO NOT** share customer names, mailing addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers, credit card numbers, account numbers or any other type of financial information with other organizations for the purpose of marketing or solicitation.

**CHOICE TO OPT-OUT** : As noted above, Checks In The Mail may use your contact information to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions in the future. If you do not want to receive these marketing communications, you may opt-out by calling 1-800-733-4443 and expressing your request. You may also make this request by mailing us at Checks In The Mail, Inc., 2435 Goodwin Lane, New Braunfels, TX, 78135. Please provide us with your name and address as it appears on your order. We will be sure your name and address are removed from our mailing list.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
We may change our privacy policy at any time. Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted on this website so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, as well as the latest updates on how we maintain the secure portions of our website.

**Your Acceptance of these Terms**  
By purchasing products or services from Checks In The Mail or using the Checks In The Mail website, you consent to the Privacy Statement for Checks In The Mail. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not purchase from Checks In The Mail. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions from this policy at any time. You agree that your continued purchases or continued use of the Checks In The Mail website following the posting of changes to these terms indicates your acceptance of our changes. 

* * *

Checks In The Mail is committed to ensuring that the information we obtain and use about consumers is accurate. You can help us maintain the accuracy of information previously provided or information we may have collected by contacting us at 1-800-733-4443 and informing us of changes or modifications.

* * *

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or would like to request your personal information not be shared with other companies for marketing of their products and services, please contact us at 1-800-733-4443 or at the address listed below.

> **Checks In The Mail, Inc.  
>  2435 Goodwin Lane  
>  New Braunfels, TX 78135**

For general questions, you may also email us at [info@citm.com](mailto:info@citm.com)

* * *

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. The following measures are in place to protect customers from unauthorized use of their information. The online store uses SSL Encryption to scramble sensitive information (like bank account and credit card data) that is being sent back and forth from the CITM™ web server to the customer's web browser. Checks In The Mail is a secured facility and all phone calls, faxes, mail and e-mail are handled by authorized personnel. In addition, all computer systems are physically secured. 

**The Checks In The Mail** online store protects your transactions with the highest levels of security. 

Our servers use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator and Communicator (version 2.0 and above), Microsoft Internet Explorer (version 3.0 and above), and AOL (version 3.0 and above) browsers. SSL encrypts all of your personal information, including your account line specification, MICR line specification, or similar form of access number or access code for a credit card account, deposit account, transaction account or other nonpublic, private information , name, and address, so that it cannot be intercepted as the information travels over the Internet between your browser and our site.

While we use Secure Socket Layer encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our user's information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our Billing department or a Customer Service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.

Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. 

The VeriSign Secure Site service, is one of the most recognized symbols of trust on the Web, and offers our customers instant access to Checks In The Mail's security data. Verisign reports that it is virtually unheard of for someone's credit card info to be stolen via the Web and misused. And in the highly unlikely event that it is, the Fair Credit Billing Act protects e -shoppers against unauthorized use of credit information, limiting liability to only $50. (source: Verisign, Inc.) 

If you have received the "Certificate Authority is Expired" message, visit Verisign.com to read their frequently asked questions and more about how to respond to the alert. You may need to upgrade your web browser. 

**Verify Our Certificate!**   
Click the image below to view the certificate information provided at Verisign's website.   

> **Test Our Secure Connection!**  
>  You can be sure that transactions are secured by looking for the following cues: - The URL in the browser window displays "https" at the beginning, instead of http.

  * In **Netscape Communicator** : The padlock in the lower left corner of the Navigator window will be closed instead of open. Netscape users can also follow these steps to see what level of encryption is protecting their transactions with your site: - Go to the Web site you want to check. - Click the Security button in the Navigator's toolbar. The Security Info dialog box indicates whether the Web site uses encryption. - If it does, click the Open Page Info button to display more information about the site's security features, including the type of encryption used.
  * In **Internet Explorer: Microsoft Internet Explorer** tells users when encryption is in use by displaying a padlock icon in the bar at the bottom of the IE window. With IE, users can find out a Web site's encryption level: - Go to the Web site you want to check. - Right-click on the Web site's page and select Properties. - Click the Certificates button. - In the Fields box, select "Encryption type." The Details box shows you the level of encryption (40-bit or 128-bit).
